question_data = [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is Batman?",
      "correct_answer": "Bruce Wayne",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Clark Kent",
        "Barry Allen",
        "Tony Stark"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the creator of the comic series 'The Walking Dead'?",
      "correct_answer": "Robert Kirkman",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stan Lee",
        "Malcolm Wheeler-Nicholson",
        "Robert Crumb"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "This Marvel superhero is often called 'The man without fear'.",
      "correct_answer": "Daredevil",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Thor",
        "Wolverine",
        "Hulk"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which universe crossover was introduced in the 'Sonic the Hedgehog' comic issue?",
      "correct_answer": "Mega Man",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Super Mario Brothers",
        "Alex Kidd",
        "Super Monkey Ball"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the alter-ego of the DC comics character 'Superman'?",
      "correct_answer": "Clark Kent",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bruce Wayne",
        "Arthur Curry",
        "John Jones"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the full first name of the babysitter in Calvin and Hobbes?",
      "correct_answer": "Rosalyn",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rose",
        "Ruby",
        "Rachel"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The main six year old protagonist in Calvin and Hobbes is named after what theologian?",
      "correct_answer": "John Calvin",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Calvin Klein",
        "Calvin Coolidge",
        "Phillip Calvin McGraw"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'Homestuck' what is Dave Strider's guardian?",
      "correct_answer": "Bro",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Becquerel",
        "Doc Scratch",
        "Halley"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'Homestuck' the Kingdom of Darkness; is also known as?",
      "correct_answer": "Derse",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Skaia",
        "Prospit",
        "The Medium"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "When was Marvel Comics founded?",
      "correct_answer": "1939",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1932",
        "1951",
        "1936"
      ]
    }
]